擎天柱！
Prime!
福勒探员 有何贵…
Special agent Fowler, to what do we owe...
还能干什么？霸天虎呗！
What else, Cons!
我把他们赶至绝路
I chased them off from some hard ordinates.
他们也把我敲了下来！
But not before they blew me out of sky.
又输了？
Hm，again?
他们想抢我的“那玩意儿”
They tried to smash and grab for the dingus.
（dingus是D.N.G.S的代称，意思是不知名的某种小装置）
哪个玩意儿？
The... what's it?
动态核能发电系统（D.N.G.S）
Dynamic Nuclear Generation System.
（dingus是D.N.G.S的代称，意思是不知名的某种小装置）
A.K.A. dingus.
也就是“那玩意儿”
是种供能原型机 我正要送到西岸去测试
It's a prototype energy source. I'm porting to the coast for testing.
太荒唐了
That's absurd.
红蜘蛛怎么会看上这种原始技术？
Why would Starscream bother with such primitive technology?
我猜他们是想制造一种大规模杀伤性武器
I'm guessing they are making a big bad primitive weapon, of mass destruction.
如果这个小东西被熔毁
If this baby would melt down
这里和周边四个州都可能受到辐射污染
it would radiate this state and the four next door.
福勒探员说没说过 他在哪个州出的事？
Eh, did Agent Fowler say which state he is currently in?
我现在束手无策 擎天柱
I’m a sittin' duck here, Prime.
我要你们打开环陆桥
I need you to spin up your bridge
在虎子们杀回来之前 火速把“那玩意儿”送到目的地
and send the dingus to its destination before the Cons come back for it.
用环陆桥传送这种极不稳定的装置 恐怕不妥
I'm afraid that sending such a volatile device through the Ground Bridge is out of the question.
如果在传送途中发生意外
If there were to be an accident during transmission
辐射产生的污染就会通过环陆桥的漩涡扩散
the radiation of which you speak could propagate through Ground Bridge vortex
会波及50个州 甚至更远
and harm all 50 states, and beyond.
你还有别的高招吗？
You got any better ideas?
啊…不必了 福勒探员
Ahh... No need, Agent Fowler.
我来负责开车
I will handle the driving.
这一路可够我受的
It's gonna be a long trip.
汽车人 出发！
Autobots, roll out.
你们的坐标已经锁定 擎天柱
We are locked on your coordinates, Optimus.
不出意外的话 你们会在日落前到达目的地
Barring any complication you should reach the drop off point by sun down.
快走啊 死老头！
Move it, gramps!
福勒探员 有这个必要吗？
Agent Fowler, is that really necessary?
别跟我说你是个“三好司机”
Uh, don't tell me one of those textbook drivers.
货物由一辆无武装的民用卡车运送
They are transporting in an un-armed civilian truck.
派地面部队出击
Send in the ground units.
知道吗 这次你帮了我的大忙 擎天柱
You know, you're saving my bacon here, Prime.
能帮上忙 我很荣幸
I am proud to be of service.
当然 要是你们和虎子在自己的地盘上打 我就更轻松了
Of course, not like I'd need your help if you and the Cons had stuck to turning up your own corner of Galaxy.
你的意思是 在我们到来之前 你们的世界是太平盛世吗？
Are you suggesting that no evil existed in your world before we arrived?
这个嘛 这是…两码回事
Well, it was a… different evil.
听听收音机怎么样？
How about some radio?
你这种人大概喜欢听乡村音乐
You seem like a Nashville sound kind of guy.
就是他
That's the one
是那个虎子把我打下来的
the Con who shot me down.
他叫什么？翼形螺母？二愣子？还是鸟人？
Who is he? Wingnut? Dingbag? Skyguy?
看看身后
Watch your rear views.
施展不开拳脚 真是浑身发痒啊 老大
Feel like a little constricted without the use of my fist here, boss.
不到万不得已 必须保持车辆形态
Remain in vehicular mode unless absolutely necessary.
居然来了一群虎子
A whole team of Cons!
什么？我没发现任何信号
What? I'm not picking up anything.
他们一定使用了屏蔽技术
They must be utilizing a cloaking technology.
停车！
Pull over.
哎呀 我好怕怕啊！
Well I'll be dipped.
袭击我们的不是霸天虎 是人类
Our assailants are not Decepticons, they are humen.
人类？
袭击我们的不是霸天虎 是人类
Humen?
人类？
拜托 敢挑衅汽车人？
Oh, please. Taking on our Bots?
他们死定了！
They are road kill!
先生们
Gentlemen
让他们停车
stop their engines.
他们是哪路的？
Who are these guys?
汽车人 保持伪装形态
Autobots, maintain your cover
使用最小武力 解除武装即可
and apply minimal force, disarmament only.
那些司机不一般
Those are not civilian drivers.
来点新鲜空气吧
Could use some air.
擎天柱 右转！
Prime, bear right!
我问什么 你就答什么！
Care to tell me everything I want to know?
希望你处理“那玩意儿”时 别这么笨手笨脚
I do hope you take better care of that dingus than you do your captives.
我是特工威廉・福勒
Special Agent William Fowler here.
报上名来！
Identify yourself!
我叫塞拉斯
I am Silas
不过你可能更熟悉另一个名字
by of greater consequence to you
我们是“机械党”
we are MECH.
给你个警告
Fair warning
我们自有办法拿到你的仪器
we will be helping ourselves to your device
不惜任何伤亡代价
even if it means inflicting cacualties.
真的吗？
Is that so?
告诉我 小塞
Tell me, Sygh?
“那玩意儿”现在的市价是多少？
What's the market price for a dingus these days?
你觉得我们是想卖掉它吗 福勒特工？
What makes you think we intend to sell it, Agent Fowler?
战争正在酝酿
There is a war brewing
世界秩序即将焕然一新
between the new world order and the newest.
胜者 必定是拥有最尖端科技的一方
And the victor, will be the side armed with the most innovative technology.
我说小塞
So Sigh
你觉得“机械党”已经掌握了最尖端技术吗？
you think MECH has all the most radical tech?
司机绝不是一般人
Definitely not civilian drivers.
回头见 小塞
Later, Sigh.
福勒探员 不要小看这个“塞拉斯”
Agent Fowler, do not take your Silas lightly.
威震天当时宣扬的正是这种理念
Megatron preached the very same ideology
后来塞博特恩爆发了大战 我们的星球毁于一旦
before plunging Cybertron into the Great War that destroyed our world.
擎天柱 准备实行第二步计划
Optimus, prepare to initiate phase 2.
向南五英里处 就是会合地点
5 miles ahead to the south,  you will reach the rendezvous point.
“向南五英里处 就是会合地点”
"5 miles ahead to the south,  you will reach the rendezvous point."
这么说 汽车人已经离开了他们的基地
So, the Autobots are outside the confines of their base
似乎正忙得焦头烂额
and sound otherwise engaged.
也就是说 他们对我们毫无防备
Which means, they will never see us coming.
找到并消灭他们！
Find them, and scrap them!
遵命 红蜘蛛陛下！
Yes, lord Starscream.
那儿就是目的地
There's our destination point.
汽车人 保持紧密队形
Autobots, keep a tight formation.
战术失误
Tactical lair
只有一个出口
only one way out.
空中支援？
Air support?
是敌还是友？
Ours or theirs?
擎天柱 有麻烦了！
Optimus, you have company.
军方怎么向自己人开火？
Military fired on one of their own?
长官 “那玩意儿”！
Sir, the dingus.
长官 好在没检测到辐射
Ugh, sir, I'm not reading any radiation.
“那玩意儿”没有熔毁
The dingus didn't melt down.
是的 确实没有
No, it did not.
福勒探员 为了你和汽车人的安全
Agent Fowler, I'm afraid that if you and we are to survive.
恐怕我们现在不得不解除伪装了
It has become absolutely necessary to drop our cover.
原来那些传言是真的
So the rumors are true.
机械生命体就站在我们眼前
Living technology stands before us
但恐怕他们长久不了
though perhaps not for very long.
作壁上观吧
Remain here.
悉听尊便
Will do.
跑了这么远
After a long road trip
终于可以变形了
it feels good to get out of the car
活动活动筋骨
stretch my legs
踢爆它几个排气管！
and kick some tailpipe.
长官 如果“那玩意儿”不在卡车上…
Sir, if the dingus wasn't in the truck..
对 这个嘛
Yes, that.
福勒特工 和巨人一起共事 千万要小心
Special Agent Fowler, you need a jung life walking among titans?
下来吧 我给你们引见引见
Come on, down. I'll introduce you.
另择吉日吧
In good time.
现在我很想知道 “那玩意儿”是如何凭空消失的
But in the moment I'm too busy wandering how the dingus might have vanished into thin air without a trace.
失陪了
Now if you could excuse me
我要去赶火车
I have a train to catch.
擎天柱！
Prime!
塞拉斯识破第二步计划了！
Silas got wise to phase two!
我知道了！
I understand!
擎天柱 能听到吗？
Prime! Do you read me?
擎天柱！
Prime!
擎天柱受了重伤！
Optimus is down!
“机械党”要去抢“那玩意儿”了！
And MECH's gonna grab the dingus.
快想想办法！
We need to think of something quick!
你是说 来个“第三步计划”？
You mean like a phase three?
好吧
OK.
开动脑筋！
Come on, think!
好吧 如果“机械党”想得到“那玩意儿”
Alright, if MECH wants the dingus
他们必须上火车
they have to get on that train.
要是我们先上车呢
What if we get on board first!
想想看 来个真人对打！
You know, run some human on human interference？
绝对不行！
Absolutely not!
没错 那等于自杀
Yea, that would be suicide.
拜托 想变成“大熔炉合众国”吗？
Hello?! The United States of Meltdown?
人命关天啊！
Lives are at stake?
是你们的命！
Yes, yours!
你们要传送的地方 不光是密闭空间
You want me to not only bridge you into a confined space
而且移动速度每小时140多公里！
but one traveling at 90 miles per hour?
我根本无法想象可能出现的意外
I can't even count the number of ways that can go wrong!
大面积错位损伤 四肢骨折 金属烧伤
Mass displacement trauma, twisted limbs, metal burn?
呃 也许没有最后那种
Well, maybe not the last one.
不管怎么说
Regardless
要把环陆桥坐标锁定在高速移动的物体上 几乎不可能
it is nearly impossible to fix Ground Bridge coordinates on something moving at that speed.
要是能…跟踪火车的坐标呢？
Would it help if we had access to the train's coordinates?
那另当…
Well...
解除他们的武装
Demobilize them.
我们进来了
We are in.
收到 杰克
I read you, Jack.
手机通讯补丁很管用
The cell phone com-link patch works.
拉夫 “机械党”的人要在车顶降落
Raf, MECH's landing on top of the train.
大概20秒后 会有个岔口
In about 20 seconds, you are gonna come to a fork.
抓紧了
Brace yourselves.
怎么回事？
What happened?
有黑客
Hacker.
初级黑客
Former hacker.
什么？
What?
我就说我们这技术不靠谱吧？
And what have I been saying all alone about our technology?
这算什么？帮我们争取10秒钟吗？
So what that buy us? 10 seconds?
拉夫失算了
Raf is using his touch.
想吃我一斧子吗？
You want a slice of this?
快来啊！
Well do you?
我也一样！
What she said!
长官！
Sir.
撤退
Retreat.
你可真勇猛
Wow, you are pretty fierce.
作战原则第一条
First rule of the combat
绝不给敌人留下战利品
never leave the enemy with the spoils.
救护车 “机械党”炸断了铁轨！
Ratchet, MECH's moved the train tracks.
快把我们传送回去！
You need to bridge us out of here.
还有那些士兵！
The soldiers, too.
我们无法跟踪火车的坐标数据！
We've lost access to the train data.
没有坐标 我就没法接你们回来！
I can't bridge you back without your coordinates.
擎天柱 “机械党”炸了铁轨 杰克和神子还在火车上
Optimus, Jack and Miko are on that train and MECH has blown the tracks!
我正赶过去
I'm on my way.
全速前进！
Maximum overdrive!
我们跳车怎么样？
Maybe we should jump?
时速可是140公里啊！
At 90 miles per hour?
要么摔死 要么烧死 你选吧
It's the impact or the meltdown, take you pick.
我们当初干嘛非来不可？
What we were thinking volunteering for this?
下次你最好先想办法来脱险
Next time your need to do a better job of talking us of the situations.
还有下次吗…
Next time?
如果我们跑到车尾 是不是能多活几秒钟？
Or we can ourselves another few seconds if we are in the back of the train, right?
神子 至少 我们能死在一起
Miko, at least, we are in this together.
拉夫 重要提示！
Raf, this is important!
一定要把我的吉他留给隔板
Make sure Bulkhead gets my guitar.
先别急着说遗言
Don't read the will just yet.
擎天柱在哪儿？
Where is Optimus?
他要赶火车
He has a train to catch.
身手不错嘛 天外来客
Well played, visitor.
但我们“机械党”不会善罢甘休
But MECH still has un-fielded advantages
我们会有办法和你们对抗的
and we will find a way to level that playing field.
就算要给你开膛破肚
Even if we have to open you up.
也要摸清你们的老底
To see what makes you tick.
擎天柱 你和孩子们…
Optimus, are you and the children
都好吗？
intact?
安然无恙 救护车
Intact, Ratchet.
危机解除了
Crisis averted.
不过我们脚下这颗星球 与想象中相去甚远
But the world in which we live is a different one than previously imagined.
这里也有本土的霸天虎…
One which is bond its own Decepticons
披着人皮的老虎
in human skin.